 [
  {
  "fx":"-3x^{4}+2x-1",
  "gx":"4x^{2}-5x+7",
  "template":"f\\left(x\\right) \\cdot g\\left(x\\right)",
  "question":"-$3$x$^{4}$+$2$x$-$1$ \\cdot $4$x$^{2}$-$5$x$+$7",
  "answer":"\\left(-3x^{4}+2x-1\\right)\\cdot\\left(4x^{2}-5x+7\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"2\\cos\\left(3x\\right)-\\tan\\left(x\\right)",
  "gx":"-2e^{x}+1",
  "template":"f\\left(x\\right) - g\\left(x\\right)",
  "question":"2$\\cos\\left(\\right.$3$x$\\left.\\right)$-$\\tan\\left(\\right.$x$\\left.\\right)$-$-$2$e$^{x}$+$1",
  "answer":"\\left(2\\cos\\left(3x\\right)-\\tan\\left(x\\right)\\right)-\\left(-2e^{x}+1\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"-10-4\\ln\\left(3x+1\\right)",
  "gx":"-\\left(2x-10\\sec\\left(3x\\right)+1\\right)",
  "template":"f\\left(x\\right) - g\\left(x\\right)",
  "question":"-$10$-$4$\\ln\\left(\\right.$3x$+$1$\\left.\\right)$-$-$\\left(\\right.$2x$-$10$\\sec\\left(\\right.$3x$\\left.\\right)$+$1$\\left.\\right)",
  "answer":"\\left(-10-4\\ln\\left(3x+1\\right)\\right)-\\left(-\\left(2x-10\\sec\\left(3x\\right)+1\\right)\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"\\sqrt{x}+x^{2}+1",
  "gx":"x-\\sqrt{x}-1",
  "template":"f\\left(x\\right) / g\\left(x\\right)",
  "question":"\\sqrt{x}$+$x$^{2}$+$1$ / $x$-$\\sqrt{x}$-$1",
  "answer":"\\left(\\sqrt{x}+x^{2}+1\\right) / \\left(x-\\sqrt{x}-1\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"2^{x}-3\\csc\\left(7x^{2}+1\\right)-2",
  "gx":"-6\\cos\\left(\\sqrt{x}\\right)+5e^{3x}+4",
  "template":"f\\left(x\\right) - g\\left(x\\right)",
  "question":"2$^{x}$-$3$\\csc\\left(\\right.$7$x$^{2}$+$1$\\left.\\right)$-$2$-$-$6$\\cos\\left(\\right.$\\sqrt{x}$\\left.\\right)$+$5$e$^{3x}$+$4",
  "answer":"\\left(2^{x}-3\\csc\\left(7x^{2}+1\\right)-2\\right)-\\left(-6\\cos\\left(\\sqrt{x}\\right)+5e^{3x}+4\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"-11",
  "gx":"x^{2}-4x+3",
  "template":"f\\left(x\\right) \\cdot g\\left(x\\right)",
  "question":"-$11$\\cdot $x$^{2}$-$4$x$+$3",
  "answer":"\\left(-11\\right)\\cdot \\left(x^{2}-4x+3\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"\\sin\\left(x+1\\right)",
  "gx":"2x^{3}-3x+1",
  "template":"f\\left(g\\left(x\\right)\\right)",
  "question":"\\sin\\left(\\right.$2$x$^{3}$-$3$x$+$1$+$1$\\left.\\right)",
  "answer":"\\sin\\left(\\left(2x^{3}-3x+1\\right)+1\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"\\csc\\left(2x\\right)",
  "gx":"x^{2}-\\sqrt{x}",
  "template":"f\\left(g\\left(x\\right)\\right)",
  "question":"\\csc\\left(\\right.$2$x$^{2}$-$\\sqrt{x}$\\left.\\right)",
  "answer":"\\csc\\left(2\\left(x^{2}-\\sqrt{x}\\right)\\right)"
  },
  {
  "fx":"4x^{5}-2x^{3}+x-10",
  "gx":"\\cos\\left(x\\right)+1",
  "template":"f\\left(g\\left(x\\right)\\right)",
  "question":"4$\\cos\\left(\\right.$x$\\left.\\right)$+$1$^{5}$-$2$\\cos\\left(\\right.$x$\\left.\\right)$+$1$^{3}$+$\\cos\\left(\\right.$x$\\left.\\right)$+$1$-$10",
  "answer":"4\\left(\\cos\\left(x\\right)+1\\right)^{5}-2\\left(\\cos\\left(x\\right)+1\\right)^{3}+\\left(\\cos\\left(x\\right)+1\\right)-10"
  },
  {
  "fx":"2\\log\\left(x\\right)",
  "gx":"\\sin\\left(7x\\right)+3\\cot\\left(x^{2}\\right)",
  "template":"g\\left(f\\left(x\\right)\\right)",
  "question":"\\sin\\left(\\right.$7$2$\\log\\left(\\right.$x$\\left.\\right)$\\left.\\right)$+$3$\\cot\\left(\\right.$2$\\log\\left(\\right.$x$\\left.\\right)$^{2}$\\left.\\right)",
  "answer":"\\sin\\left(7\\left(2\\log\\left(x\\right)\\right)\\right)+3\\cot\\left(\\left(2\\log\\left(x\\right)\\right)^{2}\\right)"
  }
  
]
